(Penny:)Okay, I got a box, but there's no key
in here. Just letters.
(Sheldon:)That's the wrong box. Put it back.
(Penny:)Oh, Sheldon, are these letters
from your grandmother?
(Sheldon:)Don't read those letters.
(Penny:)Oh, look, she calls you Moon Pie.
That is so cute.
[SHRIEKING]
Put down the letters!
(Leonard:)Hey, Penny. It's Leonard.
(Penny:)Hey, Leonard. How's the train ride?
Delightful. I don't know
what you're doing right now...
(Leonard:)...but there are little bubbles forming
in the corner of Sheldon's mouth.
(Penny:)Okay. Yeah, I kind of crossed a line.
Put him back on.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
- I'm back.
- What up, Moon Pie?
No one calls me Moon Pie but Meemaw.
(Leonard:)Hey, Penny. Leonard again.
(Howard:)So anyway, in the dream, you and I
were ice skating, just the two of us.
(Howard:)And then I picked you up
by your ankles...
(Howard:)...and twirled you round and round
until your legs tore off.